my first day of senior year, my special
day. [music]
I'm totally thrilled right now.
I'm afraid to get to school.
>> Well, I have
>> which I bring to you that [music] I want
>> [music]
[music]
>> Today just does not feel real. I can't
believe I'm saying this, but today is my
first day of senior year. All I can
think about right now is how for my
first day of freshman year, I was so
confused on how I made it that far, and
now I'm even farther and even more
confused. But, good morning everyone.
Welcome, welcome back to my channel.
This video is going to be my first day
of senior year get ready with me and
vlog. Time is currently 5:38 a.m. When I
tell you guys I could not sleep, like my
mind would not just shut off. I had so
much trouble sleeping, and I really hope
that it doesn't catch up to me later in
the day. Speaking of my day, I want to
go over my schedule for my senior year.
This feels so weird right now. I feel
like out of body. I don't know how to
explain it. Okay, I'm just going to go
down the list. First period, AP lit.
Second period, AP world. Third period,
AP bio. Fourth period, student council.
Fifth period, AP stats. And sixth
period, field bio. And then this year,
since I'm a senior, I have seventh
period early release. That's going to
feel amazing leaving the building early.
That's my first semester senior year
schedule. This doesn't feel real. I need
to like decompress. I don't know. I just
remember every single first day so
vividly, and it doesn't feel like it's
been 3 years at all. I have an amazing
feeling about today. I'm going to keep a
positive mindset. I know in the past
first days have always been like ew,
school. This is my last first day, so
there's no room to complain. And I
actually want to start the day by
journaling because I feel like today is
a very special day. I'm going to journal
really quick and then we will get ready
for my last first day of school.
I can't I actually can't handle myself.
Skin is looking great. Everyone say
thank you to
the Medicube face mask that I wore to
bed last night. I feel really weird. I
don't know how to explain it. I just
feel really weird.
Nobody play Ribs slipping through my
fingers like don't None of those songs
don't play it. No, don't play them near
me. Not today, not tomorrow, days after
that. Don't play any of that kind of
music around me. I'll start crying. I'm
going to do my skin care. Here's the
cleanser I use.
The good thing about this year is that a
lot of the teachers I've already had
before because the teachers at my
school, a lot of them teach several
subjects. So, four of the teachers that
I have this year I've already had
before. I just put on the Medicube pink
peptide serum. And for moisturizer /
SPF, this one's my favorite. Yeah, like
I said, I've already had these teachers
and two of them I'm really close with.
It's nice that I don't have to build a
billion new bonds with teachers. Now
that my skin care is done, I'm going to
I don't really need to touch up my hair.
I kind of already did with some water,
but I do want to put in the last like
three drops of this oil that I have. I'm
really running out here. My hair
actually wants to cooperate today, which
is amazing considering that it's like a
big event day cuz whenever I have
something big, my hair never wants to
work. So, more essentials, no dryness,
and no smelliness here. I'm kind of
nervous, but like the nervousness is
stemming from excitement cuz I know this
year is going to be huge and I can't
wait for football season and I already
know my workload is going to be insane
especially with college apps, which
that's a whole other journey that I
don't think I'm ready for, but I'm going
to have to tackle it day by day. And
we're actually doing pretty good for
time. It's 6:25 and I think I want to
make some phone calls because it's the
first day. I want to see what the vibe
is.
Good morning.
It's time for eye.
All right, right. No, I just wanted to
check in.
No, that's what I told the video. I was
like, "Don't play no Slipping Through My
Fingers, Ribs. Don't play NO
>> [screaming]
>> TURN IT OFF.
MAYBE, WE'LL SEE.
OKAY, WELL, two out of three people I
called just didn't pick up. Anyways, I
It's time to get dressed now. I'm going
to go dance to some music. I'm really
excited to show you guys my outfit.
Yeah, I'm going to go get dressed. I
feel like the Spider-Man backpack really
makes the whole outfit. I will show you
guys the outfit in the mirror in a
second, but I don't know I just I keep
saying that I feel weird, but I really
feel weird because this is my last time
dancing around my room getting ready for
my first day. Like
But, I made my bed, danced around to
some music. Let me show you guys my
outfit. First day of senior year,
baseball tee, these shorts with one of
my favorite belts, and then of course, I
have to wear my new loafers and my
amazing Spider-Man backpack. I'm feeling
really good about today. Let's go pack
my lunch.
Lunch box and my little mini Boo Boo, if
you guys remember.
Stanley
grapes.
Comment if you know, you know.
And then three like
bar kind of snacks cuz I know I'm going
to get hungry. Speaking of hungry, it is
time to go and get breakfast with my
friends. Oh, wait.
And a fork. And my mom also needs her
picture of me, so
What? What am I looking at? Oh.
Girl, bye. It's still here, but it's
like it's
It's dead.
We did it.
>> Okay, the plan is to get Chick-fil-A, 7
Brew.
>> No, you can't do that, Cade, because
it's actually our last time having a
first day, so there's no no complaining
allowed.
He's so giddy.
>> We're getting Chick-fil-A first.
>> Yeah.
And also 7 Brew has an app now, so
prepare to be sick.
Um and there's no
>> You can actually [clears throat] like
drink your drink
>> actually drink my drink in first period.
I don't have to put it in the fridge,
yes. This feels so weird. I have said
that like 10 times in this video
already.
>> I started getting a little sick.
>> What?
>> It's my stomach.
>> No, like my stomach kind of hurts. Maybe
it's cuz I'm hungry, I don't know. I
think I'm just
>> the first day in middle school I threw
up, so I didn't go. I was like at the
bus stop and I started puking.
>> Hi, I have three mobile orders.
>> You said two mobile orders?
>> Three.
>> Three mobile orders. What was it?
>> One for Sebastian P.
>> Can I get you a straw or a napkin?
>> No, thank you. The next one's for Kenley
B. Yeah, the last one's for Cade P.
>> For Cade P?
>> No, thank you.
>> Okay, you got a straw or a napkin?
>> Thank you.
>> My pleasure.
>> She ate that. Guys, it's really like
Silent Hill outside. It's making me
really mad. It's ugly.
Let me get my 7 Brew order. Cultivate
kindness.
I did not like that.
Um
Stop.
>> It's nice to actually see him, so I
don't say, "What are your guys'
milkshake flavors? What do you want as
your milkshake flavor?"
>> Stop. Oh my god, I'm going
>> It's going to be weird cuz this is new
to everyone.
>> guys have a fun number with us?
>> Uh well, we actually have the mobile
orders. Yeah.
>> Okay, a medium sunrise energy
and then ocean breeze energy
>> Anyways, I'm so proud of you for getting
a medium and a mobile order.
>> Ocean breeze is still good. How's your
>> Oh,
you want me hold your drink?
>> I'm chill. I'm good.
>> Oh, okay.
>> We're going to go to our beloved high
school. We're going to have
>> We need to get boluses.
>> Just made it to my new parking spot,
402.
Okay.
This is so good.
>> Why did they give me 15 napkins?
>> They knew. I don't want to hear you make
any jokes about anything AP Lit related
cuz now we're not in the same class and
it's not funny.
>> Oh, yeah. So, we're in the same AP Lit
and he's not.
>> So, it's pretty much going to be the
same last year, but you won't hear any
screaming in the background anymore. Can
you guys sit in the same seats on like
don't get food on
>> thinking about it. It's first period, we
got that.
>> Anyways,
um we're going to get out of my car,
film some TikToks. It's going to be kind
of awkward, but
we have 12 minutes until school starts.
Uh
>> Where's your [snorts] senior backpack?
>> Where's yours, Kennedy?
>> My senior backpack is back there. It's
Spider-Man.
>> That's not a senior backpack.
>> It's too sick.
>> Okay, wait. What What is that?
>> I told you to
>> Hi.
>> We're here.
>> Doomsday.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, bye.
>> Let's go.
Oh my goodness. Setting stuff up. In
your backpack.
>> It's so cute.
>> It's Barbie.
>> Cuz I would wear this hairstyle every
day.
>> I feel like that's the first normal
That's like the first normal one,
though.
>> Shouldn't be like too much
>> I still feel like a junior. I'm
emotional just getting
I feel like I'm home.
We're home.
>> I love this.
Wait, is that ours?
These are ours.
>> That's This is so adorable.
I know.
I miss Cade.
Yeah.
I'm not going to get emotional.
but
they it's like huge but it's there's
only one zipper so it's really awkward
cuz I have to like pull it from the
side.
>> Where you going to go?
>> I'm going to bed.
>> AP World.
>> I love you so much. I love you.
So mine's like 30 years old.
>> Oh. [laughter]
>> And we have two classes together.
>> And look at my flag.
>> This is our first time.
This class is funny, bro.
>> We have two classes together this year,
AP World.
>> AP World.
>> We have a class together.
My heart.
>> Wiggle my way around the room.
>> Yeah, but
>> AP World.
>> Hey, happy senior year.
>> How you feel?
>> Um I actually feel really good.
>> Yeah.
>> Ready to get ice cream after this.
I still have to get my Chromebook down.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Who wants to sit getting to know us?
>> You guys, isn't this so fun?
>> AP Bio class is the best class.
>> Finally in a class together. We have so
many people up in here.
>> I know.
>> First, look at mine. Well, I haven't
been able to show you guys because we
don't go here together.
>> Fitsky, beautiful.
>> backpack. We got the flip sequins and
then I had a comms class and she gave us
blind boxes or blind bags and I got a
little
>> That's so cute. Oop.
>> [laughter]
>> Love her.
>> Yeah, that's
Yes, field bags are so much fun to film
with.
>> First day school outfit. Yes, I like I
like I like necklaces. I did my nails
kind of hoops.
And then first day school thing.
>> The cutest.
>> Thanks. I got food today, guys.
I should have told her it was for my
kid.
I want to go home. I hate this school. I
leave next period.
I leave in 45 like an hour.
jealous
I was talking to this guy over the
summer.
>> 12
>> My social battery
It's
It's getting bad. I need to go to bed.
>> Okay.
We are at lunch.
I've decided that I'm just not going to
eat lunch because
I leave anyway at 4:00, but when I get a
little hungry, who knows?
Hi guys. Welcome back to the first day
of school. Sebastian's here for sixth
period. I'm here for three and then I
have three online as well.
>> Going back to student council.
>> Yay.
>> We're back.
It's empty.
Excuse me.
Oh my god. Ignore how I'm looking a
mess. I'm like trying to get this video
done, but field bio, I didn't know
anyone in there.
Not a single person.
>> [screaming]
>> So I didn't film at all. That's I just
wanted to put that in here. Um I talk
about it in a second, but I just wanted
to stop and say hi.
Yep.
Get me out of here. Oh my god. My social
battery by sixth period, after a whole
summer of just like me time and only my
little
amazing friends that I love so dearly,
going back to this many people for six
hours a day.
No. And also, I didn't film at all in
field bio because I don't know a single
person in there.
It's like all underclassmen except for
like two other people, but field bio as
a class seems so interesting to me, so
I'm kind of just going to have to thug
it out. We're going to get to go outside
at least once a week, so I'm really
excited for that. I'm going to try and
film. I don't know how that's going to
be, but it'll probably be a lot of fun
when we go outside. I do know we have to
like start collecting bugs like next
week, which I'm not ready to do, but
it's warm, so
first day of senior year done. I will
see you guys at home. I'm pretty sure
most of you knew where I was going to
end up as soon as I got home, but I made
a matcha trying to replenish all the
energy that I've lost.
Edited and posted a TikTok debriefing my
first day while I made this matcha. Now,
I'm actually about to do some brand work
before I go to the gym cuz the grind
really does not stop. I feel like I need
to ride the wave of productivity and
energy that's going to come with the new
school year. While I may not have any
social energy, I do have some energy to
get work done. So, that's what I'm going
to do. First day of senior year, so
good.
I'm tired.
First day of senior year, where do I
even begin? That what like a whirlwind
of emotions. I also want to like read a
little bit of my journal from the
morning because I always love giving you
guys little fun things at the end of the
video for the ones that stay. Let's see.
Today is my last first day of school. In
9 months, I will be a graduate. I feel
so weird knowing that my childhood is
having its last chapter. Every time I
wish school away, I never thought about
what it would feel like to actually be
at the end. This year, I will try my
best to not wish for time to speed up.
In fact, I want time to slow down. Every
moment I have should be appreciated and
cherished. I'm excited to see what this
year will bring. And then I went into a
bunch of yap that
it just isn't necessary, but
that's basically how I feel in a
nutshell. Nervous cuz my childhood
slipping through my fingers. Oh, all
right. Like I said, I posted a debrief
on my TikTok, but first period AP Lit,
super fun. I already know that class is
going to be like my obviously my start
to the day, but I'm going to be very
happy cuz it's a good start. Second
period AP World, love. Third period AP
Bio, going to be difficult, but like I
have lots of friends in that class and
lots of people I know I can go to for
help. Fourth period student council has
been that way since freshman year. Fifth
period AP stats, I'm still testing out
the waters. I don't really know how I
feel about it yet.
I like the teacher. Sixth period field
bio, still no friends.
Going to work on that. Going to see what
I can do. But yeah, that is all for my
first day of senior year. That's crazy.
Thank you guys so much for watching as
always. I love you so much. Have a
decent day and goodbye. Happy senior
season.